/*
   Friday, September 08, 20173:33:10 PM
   User: 
   Server: 2A308-D01\SQLEXPRESS
   Database: StudentDB
   Application: 
*/

students


Sergey is a software engineer with extensive development experience in the .NET technology stack. He is a big fan of clean, testable, and maintainable code who worked for a number of successful projects ranging from small startups to complex enterprise applications. He loves to play with new technologies and to work on his own projects to stay up to date with modern software development trends.
